ghanafilla.net 2015-12-25

# Privacy Policy | Ghana HomePage

All User information supplied by Users of Ghanafilla.net as defined under the Terms & Conditions is covered by the Data Protection Act 1998.  
Users can amend information provided at any time by contacting info@ghanafilla.net  
User information will not be disclosed to a third party without Users’ permission. User details will be used only to provide Service(s) specifically requested by the User.  
Users’ details may be transferred to another company if ownership of Ghanafilla.net changes.  
Ghanafilla.net website uses cookies. Cookies are pieces of information in the form of a very small text file, which is placed, on the Website. It can be referred to as User’s Identification Card and it helps to save site log in information for the Users. Hence, when a User accesses the Website, such User may be asked to fill out a form providing personal information and such information are packaged into a cookie and sent to us, thereafter the information is stored for later use. The cookie allows interaction between the User and Website faster and easier and makes the browsing experience more efficient and enjoyable. Users may choose not to accept cookies but this will prevent proper functioning of the Services of the Website.  
In addition to clause 6, Ghanafilla.net website includes very small files provided by one or more advertising networks that help them more precisely to target advertising to users based on user’s activity on sites within those networks.These files do not access or use information by which users can be personally identified. If you wish, you can prevent theses files from using non-personal information about you by either deleting the cookie folder in your browser or by putting your browser’s privacy setting higher, but doing so will mean that you will not be presented with advertising that reflects the way that you use our, and other, websites and may well adversely affect your experience of websites that use cookies to enhance or personalise that experience. You can find out how to make these changes to your browser at this site: http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/”  
Whenever a User requests a page, username, IP address, browser and version and operating system are stored in a log file. This information is only used for statistical purposes to help improve this site and provide accurate statistics to advertisers in the form of aggregated data.  
Ghanafilla.net cannot guarantee that third party services accessible through Ghanafilla.net services operate the same Privacy Policy.  
Ghanafilla.net reserves the right to update and change this Privacy Policy at any time. However, GhJoy.net will not use information submitted by a User under this current notice in a way not currently described herein without also notifying the User of such change, and giving the User an opportunity to opt-out, or otherwise prevent that new use of your information.  
If you have any questions concerning this Privacy Policy or would like us to amend or destroy your details please contact us at info@ghanafilla.net  
Cookies  
5.1 A cookie is a small piece of information that is placed on your computer when you visit certain websites. Find out more about the use of cookies on http://www.cookiecentral.com.

5.2 We use cookies to:

(1) remember you when you visit this website to keep track of your browsing patterns and to build up a profile of how you and other users use the website.

(2) make our website work as efficiently as possible.

(3) administer services to you and to advertisers.

5.3 Most browsers allow you to turn off cookies. To do this look at the “help” menu on your browser. Switching off cookies may restrict your use of the website and/or delay or affect the way in which it operates.

DISCLAIMER

This is a gossip type website. Some Of the Information contained on this site is reported as rumor and not actual facts unless I am talking about my own experiences. Do not take offense to any material on this site because everyone has the right to their side of the story. I am willing to hear all sides. Anyone in this industry, including myself will be subject to being put on blast. What you see is what you get! This is all for your own entertainment purposes.

The information contained in this website is for general information purposes only. The information is provided by Ghanafilla.net and while we endeavour to keep the information up to date and correct, we make no representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied, about the completeness, accuracy, reliability, suitability or availability with respect to the website or the information, products, services, or related graphics contained on the website for any purpose. Any reliance you place on such information is therefore strictly at your own risk.

In no event will we be liable for any loss or damage including without limitation, indirect or consequential loss or damage, or any loss or damage whatsoever arising from loss of data or profit arising out of, or in connection with, the use of this website.

Through this website you are able to link to other websites which are not under the control of Ghanafilla. We have no control over the nature, content and availability of those sites. The inclusion of any links does not necessarily imply a recommendation or endorse the views expressed within them…
